Microsoft Dynamics 365 Business Central
has powerful built-in capabilities to
analyze and report on data, but finding
the insights you need takes time.
Copilot simplifies analysis by
transforming raw data into insightful
summaries using next-generation AI.
Just describe what you need, and Copilot
creates totals, pivots, and filters to
help you find the information you're
looking for.
Now, you can easily explore trends and
outliers without ever leaving Business
Central.
And it's available for most Business
Central data, even your customizations,
so everyone in your organization can get
to insights faster.
Make data-driven decisions that propel
your business forward with Copilot in
Business Central.